

## ABOUT ME

28 years old

Server administrator with 5 years of experience in the Infrastructure sector, that promote improvements facilitate business processes. Through administration, coordination and analysis I have managed to follow up on various projects to optimize resources and reduce infrastructure costs.

## CONTACT



Mariano Abasolo 9, Tlalpan Centro, CP. 14000



(+52) 56 1635 8368



e.alvarado.palma@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/sandraalvarado



https://github.com/ealvaradopalma/

### LANGUAJES

English: Beginner Spanish: Native

## **EDUCATION**

System Enginner TESI (2012 - 2017)

# SANDRA **ALVARADO**

# SYSTEM ENGINEER

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### SERVER ADMINISTRATOR

Omnibus de Mèxico (2018 - 2021)

Within my work role, one of my main responsibilities was the administration of VMware, Citrix, Windows and Linux environments, based on the various requirements of the operation.

As part of the operation, I was in charge of the security of these environments, collaborating in various cases for the application of firewall policies, NAT's and web services implementations in F5.

#### INFRASTRUCTURE ADMINISTRATOR

Deloitte (2021 - present)

I coordinate, plan, and carry out activities related to the administration of the internal infrastructure of the Risk Assessment area, to integrate new solutions that require the Cybersecurity service.

I manage and execute vulnerability scans on various operation systems as well as perform their remediation and fixes. I also implement the hardening on the infraestructure before it goes into production. I generate and deliver health reports from diferents scans and solutions.

I have collaborated in the development and execution of security controls and policies to mitigate possible threats and implement strategies to reduce some security gaps in IT.

# COURSES

#### NIST CYBERSECURITY FRAMEWORK IMPLEMENTATION

**Udemy Plataform** 

Cibersecurity

# **SKILLS**

**OFFICE** 

**VMWARE** WINDOWS SERVER FIREWALL / SWITCH VEEAMBACKUP **SECURITY**